New Zealand didn 't even get to have its primary anthem ,
God Defend New Zealand , played at sporting events like the Olympics until 1972
until then , it was always God Save the Queen .
Did the cut of the film you saw start with a portrait of a young Queen Elizabeth II
get splattered with gore ?
That was a parody of what happened at cinemas in NZ in the 50s -
God Save the Queen would play , while an image of her was projected ,
and the audiences were expected to stand at attention .
[ GB anthem ends ]
[ ♪ Heartbeat exotic score ♪ ]
[ ♪ Industrial machinery noise ♪ ]
[ ♪ Industrial noise and exotic score mixed together ♪ ]
[ Footsteps crunch in the gravel ]
- Huh ! - Ah !
I 've got the vibes . This thing is evil , man .
I 've got a bad feeling .
Shut up and keep moving .
Is big mistake .
Let it go , man . We set it down and we let it go .
Ooh !
[ Monkey growls ]
[ Bird of prey shrieks ]
[ ♪ Ominous score ♪ ]
[ Winston gasp ]
It 's only a bloody monkey for Christ 's sake .
Now pick it up .
[ Gasp ]
[ ♪ Exotic score ♪ ]
Listen , if you no pick up the cage ...
You no get the big Dollars .
[ Gasps violently ]
[ Native growls ]
Shit .
[ Natives howling ]
[ Native rumble ]
Don 't move !
What are these buggers playing at ?
[ Drumbeat ]
[ Shaman hisses ]
[ Speaking native language ]
[ Monkey screeches ]
He says , the rat-monkey must be set free .
He says that we must leave this valley and never return .
Or the evil spirits will exact their revenge !
[ Speaking native language ]
Unless we leave this valley immediately , they will slit our bellies open ...
And spread our carcasses across a cave found for the bats to feast on .
Is that so ?
You tell these jokers that I have the big rubber stamp ...
From the boss man in Palembang .
Permit . Look and see , permit .
Permit . [ Paper crackles ]
[ Paper rip off ]
[ Native rumble ]
[ Contract crackles ]
[ Tear up treaty ]
[ Stuart screams ] [ Winston groans ]
[ Gun loading clicks ]
[ Growling angrily ]
I 'm a New Zealand zoo official .
And this monkey is going to New town .
[ Continuous fire ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Shout confusion ]
[ Clack ]
[ Blade clang ]
No ! No ! No !
[ Clang ]
[ Monkey grunting ]
Move it !
[ Natives howling ]
[ Winston screams ]
[ Gravel crunch ]
[ Growl ]
[ Native roars ]
[ More roaring ]
[ Gravel crunch ]
Start her up ! Quick !
[ Clack noise ]
[ Scratching ]
[ Monkey screeches ]
[ Cry for help ] Hey !
[ Warriors shouting ]
Drive you buggers !
Ow !
Hey ! Wait !
Step on it !
Stewart !
[ Warriors shouting ]
Wait ! Please !
[ Creaking ]
- [ Monkey screeches ] - [ Stewart ] Ouch !
[ Winston laughs ] Ha ! Ha ! Ha-ha-ha !
[ Winston laughs ] Ha ! Ha ! Ha ! Oh !
[ Arrow clicks ]
The little bugger bit me .
Zingaya .
Zingaya !
[ Brakes squeak , wheels rasp ]
[ Groans ]
Huh !
[ Thud ] [ Gasp ]
[ Anxious groan ]
[ Gravel crunch ] [ Anxious groan ]
You 've got the bite .
There 's ... there 's some Dettol in the jeep .
[ Anxious groan ]
[ Groans ]
[ ♪ High Tension score ♪ ]
Oh , jeez , no !
[ Scratching in the gravel ]
No ! What are you doing ?
[ Crunch ] [ Screaming ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Gasp ]
Zingaya .
Oh , shit .
[ Scream ]
[ Hyperventilation ]
- Zingaya ! - Zingaya !
[ Stuart Hyperventilation ]
[ Screeching ] Ahhh !
[ ♪ Braindead theme score ♪ ]
[ ♪ Idyllic score ♪ ]
CAUTION : LIVE ANIMAL DO NOT HANDLE DESTINATION : WELLINGTON ZOO NEW ZEALAND
[ Monkey screeches ]
[ Gasps ]
No !
[ Banknotes rustling ]
[ Airplane door squeaks and bangs ]
[ Engines thunder ]
[ Airplane roars ]
[ Hissing ]
[ Thunder ]
[ ♪ Cheerful piano music ♪ ]
[ Engines howl ]
[ Monkey screeches ]
[ Tailgate squeaks ]
[ Bang ]
[ Tram bell clang clang ]
[ Gearbox rattles ]
[ ♪ Carillon score ♪ ]
[ Car engine noise ]
[ Handbrake noise ]
[ Car door clicks ]
[ Tailgate clicks ]
[ Cash register crank Rattles ]
[ Cash register rings ]
[ Money jingles ]
Thank you .
[ Man whistling ]
Hi , Paquita .
Good morning , Roger .
[ Pen click ] That 's the lot .
Tell your dad that I 'll be round on Thursday with the saveloys .
That 's a pretty dress , Paquita .
[ Gentle scrubbing ]
See you later , alligator .
[ Paquita sighs ] [ Rogers ' car door slams ]
[ Claps lightly ] [ Paquita moans ]
You like that boy , Paquita ?
[ ♪ Subtle piano score ♪ ]
Shuffle the cards .
[ Rubbing and clicking ]
We will see if you and Roger are destined to be together .
[ Sighs ]
Create his image in your mind .
And cut the cards .
Paquita ?
I thought we had seen the last of this .
But there you go , you start over again .
[ Smacking ]
[ The card click ]
This ...
Is you .
And this ...
Is the man of your future .
But he doesn 't look like Roger .
It is not Roger !
[ ♪ Dark score ♪ ]
[ The card clicks ]
There will be one romance .
And it shall last forever .
Romance .
Pooh !
What about money ?
This man ...
Will enter your life ...
In the near future .
And you will become ...
Romantically entangled with him .
almost immediately .
But who is it ?
You will recognize this man ...
[ The card clicks ]
By the symbol ...
Of the star ...
And of the moon .
What is this ?
No ! No ! Not that one !
[ Doorbell ringing ]
Paquita , we have a customer .
It 's bad , yes ?
Oh ...
Paquita !
[ Door curtain rattles ]
[ Paquita exhales loudly ]
[ Dull bang ]
[ Packaging crackles ]
Uh , just dropping of our order .
[ Paper crackles ]
[ Unfolds paper ]
Um ...
Mom says to pack the biscuits on top , because she doesn 't want any broken .
Uh , actually ...
[ Door curtain rattles ]
I 'll take one of these now .
[ Pencil clatter ]
[ ♪ Exciting score ♪ ]
[ Door curtain rattles ]
Sorry .
[ Gasps ]
[ ♪ Illumination piano score ♪ ]
Santa Maria .
[ Rumble and clatter ]
Better be off then .
[ Clang clang clang ]
[ Rail noise ]
[ Hiss ]
[ Clang ]
[ Rail noise ]
[ Vera ] Lionel !
[ ♪ Aggressive piano score ♪ ]
[ Vera ] Lionel ? !
[ Footsteps knock ]
[ Woman on radio ] Good morning , everybody .
Morning , everybody . Well , now I 'd like ...
There 's a beetle .
Eh ?
There , under the fridge .
[ Stick knocks ]
Horrid little creature scuttled right in front of me .
I thought I told you to spray this house .
The place is infested with vermin .
I 'll get on to that straight away , mum .
[ Crackles ]
Lionel ?
[ High heels click ]
You 'll be pleased to know that your mother has been voted treasure elect ...
Of the WLWL . [ Slaps knife on paper ]
The Wellington Ladies Welfare League .
That 's great , mum .
And on Friday , the president , Nora Matheson ...
Is dropping by to offer her congratulations .
Wow , the president .
Oh , God !
Look at the state of this place .
[ High heels click ]
All the windows will have to be polished .
Whiter , brighter , cleaner wash .
Look at this dust . It 's an inch thick .
[ Knife clangs ]
You 'll have to do the silver .
I polished it last week .
And the drapes need cleaning .
Once a week , once a month ...
I just moved the lawn .
Does this look like a well maintained frontage ?
Very often after drying the dishes ...
[ Mower noises ]
[ Mower blades howl ]
[ Mower rattles ]
[ Scratching noise ]
Whoa ! Aah !
[ Giggles ]
Get off , you stupid dog .
[ Groans ]
Here , I 'll help you .
No , I manage .
Your brother usually does the deliveries .
Not today .
[ Sigh ]
Ohhh , is a big house .
You live here always ?
Yeah .
[ Dog panting ]
You like my dog ?
It 's very big , yes ?
Any bigger and he 'd belong in a zoo .
Zoo , pardon ?
The zoo , you know ...
Animals ?
Cages ?
Ahhh ...
Claro .
I 'd like to go with zoo .
I go with the zoo ?
Oh , no . No , no .
You want to go to the zoo .
Yes , please .
Oh ho .
Okay .
Tomorrow ?
[ ♪ Oppressive score ♪ ]
[ Clattering ]
[ Crunch ]
I 'll meet you outside the shop .
Okay .
[ Glass shatters ]
[ ♪ Oppressive score ♪ ]
I have to go .
[ Footsteps knock ]
[ Door rumbles ]
My jardiniere , it shattered .
Oh , mum , that was your favorite .
It would never have happened if you 'd taken more care with the dusting .
I can get you another one .
It 's irreplaceable .
A present from your father .
Our last wedding anniversary .
Before ...
He was taken from us .
[ Sobs ]
I miss him too .
[ Vehicle engine starts ]
[ ♪ Playful score ♪ ]
[ Lion roars ]
[ Click ]
[ Snort ]
[ Paquita laughs ]
[ Lion roars ]
Oh ...
Look !
Gary Grant ? He is such a dream .
I wish I could be Grace Kelly .
She 's so pretty .
That beautiful blonde hair .
[ ♪ Ominous score ♪ ]
[ Splashing ]
[ Drastic score ]
Lionel ?
What is wrong ?
[ Sighs ]
Sorry .
Um ...
When I was young , I was at the beach and I ...
I nearly drowned .
When I fell off this pier .
Uh , my dad dived in to save me , but ...
As he was climbing out this ...
Freak wave just ...
Washed him out to sea , and ...
He drowned .
[ ♪ Tragic score ♪ ]
Oh , the little monkeys , look Lionel .
[ ♪ Playful score ♪ ]
[ Monkey squeaks ]
[ Paquita laughs ]
[ Lionel laughs ]
[ Smacking ]
[ ♪ Cheerful score ♪ ]
[ Screeches ]
[ Monkey squeaks ]
[ Dull bang ] [ Monkey squeaks ]
[ Monkey squeaks funny ]
There , for you .
[ Dull Thud ]
[ ♪ Dark exotic score ♪ ]
- [ Aggressive growling hissing ] - [ Paquita ] Ahhh !
[ ♪ Exotic score ♪ ]
[ Growls ]
[ Hiss ]
[ ♪ Exotic score becomes more dramatic ♪ ]
[ Growls ]
[ Scratchy Crack ]
Ahhh !
[ Growls ]
[ Crunched bite ]
Ahh !
[ Grunting ]
[ Screech ]
[ Growling ]
[ Exotic birds singing ]
Poor little bugger .
Whoa ! Ooh !
[ Growls ]
You , get out of there , you vicious , little shit !
- [ Exotic birds singing ] - [ Zoo keeper groans ]
Reckon they 're only found on one island , you know .
Story goes these great , big rats ...
Come scuttling of the slave ships .
And raped all the little tree monkeys .
You know , the natives use them in black magic rituals .
- Really ? - Yeah .
Don 't ask me how .
Probably suck the blood of virgins , eh , eh ?
I want to sit down .
Wow .
Mmmh !
Sorry .
Now hold still , Brett .
Smile !
[ ♪ Ominous score ♪ ]
Huh ? !
[ Bush rustles ]
- [ Slushy noise ] - [ Mom ] Oh ! Oh !
[ Growls ]
Ahhh !
Ah !
Aha ?
Mum ? !
Ah !
[ Crushing ]
Ugh !
[ Growls ]
[ Slam ]
[ Bang ]
Argh !
[ Crackles ]
[ Vera ] Grrr !
[ Crunch ]
Ahhh !
[ Splash ]
Ew !
Ew .
[ Sludge ]
Oh !
[ Another monkey squeaks ]
[ Gasps ]
Mum ? !
[ Monkey squeaks ]
Holy shit !
Look at this ! It bit me .
I 've been savaged !
And my dress .
Here , I help you .
Ah !
Ah ! Ah !
Lionel ?
Take me home .
[ Sighs ]
[ ♪ Sad Score ♪ ]
There you are , Vera .
Now you just rest up .
I 'll be back in a couple of days to change that dressing .
Thanks , nurse McTavish .
It 's all right , Lionel , I 'll see myself out .
[ Sighs heavily ]
How about a cup of tea ?
I don 't think you have any idea of the pain and anxiety you 've caused me .
I thought you were a trustworthy boy , but going out behind my back with that ...
That oily shop girl .
Kissing and cuddling in public .
- Mum . - Don 't interrupt me .
- Mum , she 's ... - I 'll tell you what she is .
She is experienced .
Why have deliberately gone out of your way to upset me ?
I 'm sorry .
It won 't happen again .
[ Owl calls ]
I don 't deserve all this attention , darling .
If you need anything during the night , you just call .
You 're so good to me .
Night , mum .
[ Switch clicks ]
[ Door clicks ] [ ♪ Dark score ♪ ]
[ ♪ Dark score ♪ ]
[ Footsteps knock ]
[ Click ]
[ Snap lock clicks ]
[ Groan ]
Lionel ?
[ ♪ Bright piano score ♪ ]
Hello !
Shh ...
Keep your voice down !
Look , I have your jacket .
Yeah , I 'll get it tomorrow .
What ?
[ Crickets chirping ]
[ Mumbles ]
[ Giggles ]
[ Stomping ]
[ Door rattles ] [ Gasp ]
[ Sigh ]
[ Door clicks ]
Ah !
Ouch !
It could have waited till the morning .
Is that all you have to say ?
[ Sigh ]
Look , I ' m really sorry about the zoo , Paquita .
It 's just mum .
She 's ...
You know .
We go out again ?
To a movie ?
Look .
I 'd like to .
But it 's not ...
It 's just not possible .
Not possible ?
But we are romantically entangled .
Entangled ?
Huh !
Oh . Look .
Look , I don 't know what you 're thinking , but ...
I just can 't see you anymore .
Oh , Paquita .
There will be one romance .
And it shall last forever .
[ ♪ Dramatic score ♪ ]
[ Moaning ]
Oh , no .
[ Blood rushing and pulsation ]
[ The card clicks ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Pulsation ]
[ The card clicks ]
[ Moaning ]
Ooh hoo hoo !
Ahhh !
Oh oh oh !
[ Muddy and bubbling sound ]
[ ♪ Longhorn Shaman score ♪ ]
[ Amulet chain rattles ]
[ Shamanic chant ]
[ Clattering ]
[ Door rattles ]
[ Whistling ]
[ Clattering tablet ]
[ Loud footsteps ]
[ Loud tearing ]
Oh , wow ! Mum , what a beautiful day .
[ Vera groans ]
[ ♪ Dramatic score ♪ ]
[ Wheezing ]
Oh !
Mmmh !
Ew !
[ Bandage crackles ]
Ow !
[ Crackles ]
[ Wound smacking ]
[ Wring out swab ]
Ow !
[ Smacking ]
- [ Bones crunching ] - Oh !
[ Bones crunching ]
I 'm going to call nurse McTavish .
No , you 'll do no such thing . I 'm perfectly all right .
[ Lionel Hiccup ]
[ Dull thud ] [ Dark score ]
[ ♪ Dark score ♪ ]
You look after me , Lionel .
[ Doorbell rings ]
Nora Matheson .
Ladies Welfare League .
[ Loud footsteps ]
Mother is expecting us .
[ ♪ Hectic score ♪ ]
The Mathesons are here .
[ Gasp ]
[ Rumbles ]
No , mum , you 're not well .
[ Grunting ] [ Rumble ]
[ Hoarse ] Get my dress .
[ Clinking bottles ]
[ Scratching noise ]
[ Lionel rumbles in the closet ]
Oh .
Jeez !
Please go back to bed , mum . I 'll put them off , it 's only the Mathesons .
It 's the WLWL .
[ Drawer rumbles ]
[ Groans ] Oh !
[ Grunting ] Oh !
[ Grunting ]
Careful , it 'll stick on crooked .
[ Silverware clacking ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Mother wheezing ]
Our ...
Main objective next year is to ...
Try to get some of the younger generation involved in the league .
That 's why I 'm so pleased you 're on the committee ...
[ Gasps ]
Thank you , Nora .
It 's a great ...
Honor .
[ Fork clicks ]
Have you had any thought on the agenda for the annual meeting ?
Annual meeting .
An ...
[ Retching ]
[ Dish clatters ]
What we need is another war !
Yes , dear .
I hear sir Edmund Hillary is planning an attempt on the South Pole .
[ Rumbles ]
By Tractor .
[ Crunches ]
Have some more beans , Mrs. Matheson .
I 'll have a few of those , lad .
I really think we should be going , dear .
Thank you , Lionel .
What ?
No pudding ?
[ Tablet clatters ]
Only custard , I 'm afraid .
Custard !
I haven 't had a good custard in years .
She never makes the stuff .
[ Sniffs ]
[ Clicks ]
[ Muddy and bubbling sound ]
Damn fine custard .
Mmmh . [ Slurping sound ]
[ Slurping sound ]
Rich and creamy , just the way I like it .
[ Slurping sound ] [ Spoon clicks ]
[ Crackles ]
[ Splash ]
[ Slurp ]
[ Spoon scratches the plate ]
[ Increasing horror score ]
[ Cartilage crackling ]
[ Gag reflex ]
Touchy on the old food front , eh ?
[ Door closes ]
Never mind .
That was a fine meal , boy .
Thank you , Mr. Matheson .
[ Earring hits the table ]
Is it my imagination ?
Or is your mother a bit off color today ?
I don 't know .
Uh .
Right you are , boy .
[ Door slams ]
[ Loud rattling ]
[ Footsteps knock ]
Oh God , mum . [ Lionel gasps ]
Don 't let them take me away .
I 'll look after you , mum .
I promise .
[ Scrub ] [ Groan ]
[ Brush into the water ]
Lionel !
What 's wrong ?
Lionel , you must listen to me .
Dark forces are merging against you .
[ Dog paws clatter while galloping ]
My grand mama has seen it .
She said : ...
The path of hate is one of fear .
And great danger .
Ay !
- [ Dog barks ] - [ Mum screaming ]
- [ Dog growling ] - [ Mum screaming ]
Fernando !
[ ♪ Deep hectic score ♪ ]
Paquita , wait !
[ Gasp ]
God , mum !
[ Groans ]
[ Crackling slimy noise ]
[ Squeezing sound ]
[ Groans ]
Oh , Fernando !
Your mother ate my dog !
Not all of it .
[ Paquita cries ]
[ Roars ]
[ Lionel ] Oh !
[ Paquita ] Uh !
[ Groans ]
[ Vera gasps ]
[ Lionel screams ]
- [ Paquita gasps ] - [ Clatter down the stairs ]
[ Vera groans ]
Get nurse McTavish , quick !
[ Footsteps click ]
- [ Vera gasps ] - [ Lionel groans ]
[ Vera gasps ]
[ Moans ] Oh !
How long has your mother been like this ?
Since this morning .
Oh ... Um ...
I 'll call an ambulance .
You pack some things for the hospital .
I 'll do it .
[ Footsteps knocks ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Vera falls silent ]
Nurse McTavish ?
[ Phone receiver bangs ]
[ Lionel groans ] [ Sad piano score ]
[ ♪ Sad piano score ♪ ]
Your mother is dead , Lionel .
[ Lionel moans ]
[ Lionel cries ]
[ Cries ]
I 'm sorry , Lionel .
There was nothing we could do .
[ Cries ]
You 're not alone .
There 's a lot of people that care about you .
We 'll all help .
I 'll make the arrangements .
You don 't have to worry about a thing .
[ Cries ]
[ Crumpling and rumbling ]
She love you ...
Very much ... [ Thunder ]
[ Crushing bones ]
[ Nurse ] Oh Lionel ! Help ! [ Crushing bones ]
[ Vera bawl ]
[ Screams ]
[ Nurse gargles ] [ Blood hisses ]
[ Vera roars ]
Ahhh !
[ Radio playing ] ... Uh ... Ouch !
[ Sketch music ]
[ Clicks ]
Which toothbrush ?
Grrr ...
Lionel ?
Your mothers toothbrush , the white one or the green one ?
Grrr . Green !
[ Vera grunts ] Lionel
[ Vera growls and grunts ]
[ Lionel gasps ]
[ Vera grunts ]
[ Radio : Phil ] Mother , you are looking well today .
[ Mom ] I woke up this morning and I feel a 100 % better .
[ Phil ] How about a nice cup of tea ? I 'll just put the jug on .
[ Vase shattered ]
Sorry mother , that were your favorite teapot .
It slipped out me hand .
[ Mom ] Never mind that .
[ Radio broadcast ends ]
[ Footsteps knock ]
[ Vera growls ]
[ Rattling hissing ]
Whoa ! ... Ahh ! ... Ahh !
[ Vera and McTavish grunts ] [ Lionel screams ] Ah ah !
[ Zombies babble and grunt ]
[ Grunting ]
- [ Screw scratches ] - [ Lionel groaning ]
[ Roars ] Love me !
[ Smacky thud ]
- [ Nurse gurgling ] - [ Vera growling ]
[ Rumble down the stairs ]
[ Gurgling ]
[ Rumbling to the ground ] [ Gurgling stops ]
Do it !
Yeah !
You !
[ Nurse screams ]
Whoa ! [ Rumbling ]
[ Rumbling ]
[ Door slams shut , lock rattles ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Paquita ] Bed jacket , nightgown .
Slippers and toothbrush .
Where 's your mother ?
She 's gone to hospital .
I didn 't hear the ambulance .
I know .
[ Pounding on door ]
Uh ! Uh ! ...
No ... um ...
She went in Mrs. McTavish 's car .
Yeah ...
Sort of uh ...
Well sort of ...
Sort of lying across the backseat really .
Her and Mrs. McTavish off to hospital .
He !
But her night bag ?
I 'll take that .
[ Growling and pounding on door ]
[ Dog barking ]
[ Coughs ]
[ Radio man 1 ] So , it 's you who has been poaching my rabbits ?
Lionel ?
I have a good mind to let you have it with both barrels .
[ Man 2 ] But it weren 't me , sir . It was that Johnny Morris that did it .
Well , I go now .
[ Man 1 ] You just be on your way , young lad .
And if I see you here again ...
I 'll give you what for !
[ Radio broadcast ends ]
[ Wolf howling ]
[ Growling and moaning ]
[ Door rattles ]
[ Door squeaks ]
[ Bubbling ]
[ Scrubbing and juicing ]
[ Door creaks ]
What do you want ?
[ Snuffle ]
You 're not from the immigration ?
I told you people I lost my bloody papers , okay ?
My family left Latvia .
During the occupation .
We were hunted like dogs !
I just want to buy some ...
Sedatives .
What do you think I am , a goddamn doctor ?
I don 't sell sedatives .
[ Sniffing ]
Tranquilizers I do have .
But not for the general public .
[ Paper scratches ]
[ Click ]
[ Footsteps knocks ]
[ Exhale loudly ]
[ Paper claps ]
It 's lucky for you your uncle Heinrich is a pretty good joker , uh ?
[ Fabric tears ]
Do you want a syringe ...
[ Cluck ] Or are you going to sniff ?
[ Door rumbles and creaks ]
[ Stair step creaks ]
[ Rumbles ]
[ Rattles ] [ Knocks ]
[ Stair step creaks ]
[ Excited breathing ]
[ Heavenly breathing ]
[ Liquid hisses ]
[ ♪ Exciting score ♪ ]
[ Metal barrels rattle ]
[ Rumbles to the ground ]
[ Cutter engine noise score ]
[ ♪ Tension score ♪ ]
Woah !
[ Groans ]
[ Hiss ] Oh oh !
Oh !
[ Gasp ]
[ Gurgling ]
[ Switch clicks ] [ Mum hisses ]
[ Clicking sound ]
[ Demonic grunting groaning ]
[ Crunch ]
[ Squeaks ]
[ Wailing growl ]
- [ Groan ] - [ Groan ]
[ Splashing noise ]
[ Rushing sound ]
[ Splashing ] [ Screaming gurgling ]
[ Hyperventilated ]
[ Tram brake squeaks ] [ Railway track noise ]
[ Railway track noise ]
[ Footsteps quiet clicking ]
Oh , Lionel , I am happy to see you .
Tell me about these ...
Dark forces .
Death surrounds him .
There will be torment .
And suffering .
You are marked !
[ ♪ Dramatic score ♪ ]
Lionel .
Lionel , if something is wrong , I can ...
Nothing 's wrong , okay ?
[ ♪ Danger signaling score ♪ ]
[ Ululation ]
It contains the power of the white light .
It will protect you .
Keep it with you always .
[ Chain rattles ] [ Serious score ]
[ ♪ Serious score ♪ ]
[ High Heels clicking ]
[ Dull bang ]
[ Door curtain rattles ]
How is your mother ?
Oh , fine .
Yeah , they want to keep her in hospital for a few more days .
[ Heels clicking ]
[ Grunt ]
[ Bell rings : ring ring ring ]
[ Howling roaring ]
[ Window glass clinking ]
[ Grinding noise ]
[ Paquita screaming ]
- [ Grunt ] [ Paquita screaming ]
- [ Vera groans ] - Ouch !
[ Moaning ]
Ooh !
[ Lionel groans ]
[ Grunt ]
[ Gasps ]
Huh !
I didn 't see her ! She ran right in front of me .
They must have discharged her early .
[ ♪ Confident score ♪ ]
[ Church bell rings ]
[ ♪ Organ music sounds ♪ ]
It was a dreadful shock , losing Vera like that .
I had lunch with her only last Friday . Picture of health .
That boy of hers , where is he ?
Fine lad .
Lionel called half a dozen times in the last two days .
Very keen to view the remains .
Uh , of course I had to put him of , it would be far to distressing .
As it is , it has been a damn difficult embalming job .
Oh , my God . Excuse me .
[ Tires screech ]
[ Car engine ]
[ Click ]
[ ♪ Obscure clarinet score ♪ ]
I can tell you 're not a Cosgrove .
Far to good looking .
Pardon ?
Les is the name . I 'm Lionel 's ...
U –
[ Hiss ]
[ Gasp ]
Lionel 's uncle ?
And who might you be ?
Paquita Maria Sanchez .
[ Gasp ]
Latin , eh ?
Excuse me , father , I 'm looking for Lionel ?
I haven 't seen him and if he 's not here in 10 minutes ...
His mother will be delivered into the hands of the Lord in his absence .
[ Gasp ]
[ Footsteps shuffling gait ]
[ Door lock rattles ]
[ Machines running ]
[ Bubbles and steam sounds ]
[ Crackle ]
[ Crunch ]
[ Rattling noise ]
[ Mortician ] You , idiot !
I told you to stay in there .
The embalming machine should have been turned off half an hour ago !
[ Crunch ]
[ Formaldehyde fountain , hissing ]
Cranial blowout .
[ Fountain , hissing ]
[ Laughs ]
[ Crunch and hiss ]
[ Rattles ]
[ Groan ]
[ Bubbly ]
[ Mortician ] You 're a halfwit !
[ Smack ] Uh !
This is coming of your wages .
- I 'll fix the mop . - No leave it !
We 've got to get the body to the service .
Ew !
[ Plop ]
[ ♪ Organ music ♪ ]
Knew Vera , did you ?
I was her brother .
Very close we were .
Terrible occasion .
Yeah ...
I 'll be needing a few stiff drinks after this .
Would you ...
[ Gasp Moaning ]
Care to join me ?
[ Hissing ]
You look like you could do with a bit of a stiff one yourself .
Se me quita de yo que te quita la mierra y dejame en paz gillipollas .
Cool ...
Fiery .
The theme of today 's service is the sanctity of motherhood .
Vera Cosgrove will be surely missed by her friends and grieving family .
For she was indeed a fine woman .
And everything a boy could wish for in a mother .
- [ Blow up ] - [ Choking ] U – ! O – !
- [ Vera Growls ] - [ Choking ] U – ! O – !
Though deprived of his father at an early age .
Was blessed with an abundance of mother love .
[ Father McGruder ] Though our dear ones depart .
They live on in our hearts and memories .
Until in the fullness of time we too ...
Depart from this world .
[ Groaning ]
Until we are reunited once again .
- [ Groaning ] - [ Growling ]
A Christians spirit is eternal .
Whoa !
Yeah , who so ever believed in the lord Jesus Christ shall be .
[ Crowd gasps ]
Resurrected .
[ Les laughing ]
Poor Lionel .
He was always dreadfully attached to his mother .
I 've seen some displays of grief in my day , but nothing quite like that .
[ Footsteps patter ]
Do you need anything ?
I 'm fine .
I called to see you yesterday , but ...
You didn 't answer the door .
I just want to be left alone for a while , okay ?
[ Shoe heels clicking ]
At least he 's well provided for .
Yes , well , the Cosgroves were hardly paupers .
He 'll be the sole beneficiary .
[ ♪ Dark fate score ♪ ]
[ ♪ Exciting score ♪ ]
[ Engine and tire-road noise ]
[ Rumbles ]
[ Clatters ]
[ Shovel clangs ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Chop noise ]
[ ♪ Exciting music becomes more intense ♪ ]
[ Twig snaps ]
[ ♪ Shrill tone ♪ ]
Huh !
[ Thud ]
[ Liquid sloshes fine clinking ]
Hey , guys !
Look what I found .
[ Stomping steps ]
What are you doing with this thing ?
[ Liquid sloshes ]
Digging up a few stiffs ?
Hey , Void .
I reckon he 's one of those guys that rudes corpses .
Yeah , one of them macrofiliacs .
Necrophiliac , you stupid asshole .
[ Stuttering ] I bet he 's got girlie 's grots on under his strides .
Ha ! Haha !
[ Disparaging laughter ]
Shut up !
You know what you are ?
A bloody sicko .
[ A dull punch ]
Yeah , mental .
[ Spiteful laughs ]
[ Thud ]
[ Dull kicks ] [ Groaning ]
Get his wallet .
[ Dull kicks ] Ah !
[ Dull kicks ] [ Groaning ]
[ Opens fly-zipper ]
[ Spiteful laughs ]
[ Pee splashing ]
That 's my mother your pissing on .
[ Piss drumming ]
[ Whoosh ]
Uh ... uh ... uh !
[ Yodeling-yowling ] Ououou ! ... [ Vera grunting ]
It 's a zombie !
- [ Snarl and hiss ] - [ Screaming ]
[ Splash and hissing ]
[ Vera roars ]
[ Void screaming ]
[ Void rumbles to the ground ]
Ah !
Ahhh !
[ Vera grunting ]
[ Bones crushing ]
No !
[ Lionel groans ] Huh !
[ Hiss ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Steps knock ]
What in God 's name is going on here ?
[ Zombie roaring ]
[ ♪ Shrill score ♪ ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Zombie grumble ]
[ Drumming footsteps ]
The Devil is amongst us .
Stay back , boy .
This calls for divine intervention .
Ahhh !
[ ♪ Organ fanfare ♪ ]
[ Vera howls ]
[ Whines growls ]
[ Battle Cry ]
[ Both groans ]
[ Whoosh ]
I kick ass for the Lord !
[ ♪ Organ fanfare ♪ ]
[ Both groan ]
[ Hard bang ]
[ Whoosh ]
[ Thud ] [ Yowls ]
- [ Whoosh ] - [ Scream ]
[ Hard bang ]
[ Father ] Uh-ra !
[ Void ] Brrr ! [ Father ] Huh eh ! [ Bang ]
[ Thud ]
[ Father ] Uh ! [ Growling ]
[ Bang ] [ Yowls ]
[ Yowls ]
- [ Loud crack ] - [ Yelping zombie ]
[ Bang ] [ Growling ]
[ Father ] Roo uh !
[ Groaning ] [ Bang ]
[ Blood bubbling ]
[ Bang ]
[ Zombie growls ]
[ Tearing off crunching ]
[ Barks ] Ya ! Ya !
[ Growling ]
[ Bang ]
[ Whoosh ] [ Bang ]
[ Bubbles ]
[ Yelp ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Bubbles ]
[ Scream ] [ Bubbles ]
- [ Bang ] - [ Void ] Ooh !
[ Father ] Ahhh !
[ Shatter bang ]
[ Screaming ] Aah !
[ Squeezed flesh ] Aahhh !
- [ Lionel ] No ! - [ Father McGruder ] Ahhh !
Ah ! Aah !
Ahhh !
Ahhhhh !
[ Squeezed flesh ] Ah ! Ah !
[ ♪ Organ music ♪ ]
[ Grunting ]
[ ♪ Sad organ score ♪ ]
[ Thud ] [ Sad organ score ]
[ ♪ Serious organ score ♪ ]
[ Splashes ]
[ Clinking and knocking ]
[ Clatter ]
[ Tapping footsteps ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Slurping ]
[ Panting ]
[ Clatter ]
Here you are , mum .
[ Bowl knocks ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Spoon tapping ]
[ Tablet clatter ]
[ Sight ]
Void !
Use the spoon .
[ Spoon knocks ]
[ Squishy smacking ]
[ Clearing throat ]
[ Bubbling ]
[ Void grunts ]
[ Lionel sighs ] [ Void grunts ]
[ Squeeze crunch ]
[ Void grunts ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Gurgling bubbling ]
[ Burps ]
[ Sounds mushy ] [ Void grunts ]
[ Void stomps ]
[ Grunting ] [ Clapping on table ]
[ Moans ] Oh !
[ Grunts with helium voice ] Hey ! Hey !
[ Gurgling ]
[ Void whines ]
[ Scrub noise ]
[ Both grunt ]
[ Grunt ]
Hey ! Hey !
Cut that out .
[ Doorbell rings ]
Good now !
Shh .
[ Door lock rumble ]
[ Door bang ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Door lock rumble ]
How 's it going , Lionel ?
[ Zombies grunt ]
[ Thud ]
Come on , mate , I 'm dying for a slash , huh .
I 've got a urinary infection .
Christ what a stink .
Yeah , a dog must have got caught under the house and died .
[ Zombies knock on the door ]
Can 't have been easy for you these past few weeks , Lionel .
Not with your mother gone .
[ Opens fly-zipper ]
Ow !
Eh !
[ Bladder stone clinks ] Ow !
Whose that eh ...
Little girl you have been seeing ?
What ?
[ Groans ]
You know , the little Latin number with the cute bum ?
[ Lionel ] Paquita .
Oh yeah , Paquita .
That 's the one .
She 's a bit of all right .
Wouldn 't mind her doing the growl on me .
[ Flushes toilet ]
[ Heels clicks ]
So .
All this is , eh ...
Coming your way ?
Of course ...
Your mother was always intending to leave me a bequest .
- Oh . - Oh , yes .
We talked about it many times .
It was a foregone conclusion , really .
Just with her dying suddenly , she ...
Didn 't get the change to include me in her will .
Oh , well , you have to talk to the lawyers about it , uncle Les .
Don 't bring the bloody lawyers into it .
[ Hiss ]
This is a private family matter .
[ Moaning ]
What the hell is that ?
[ Gasp ]
It 's the pipes . They do that sometimes .
That 's not the pipes , Lionel . That 's somebody doing the business .
Please , uncle Les , you 've just got to leave .
[ Moaning ]
So you found your dads old stag movies ?
[ Rumbling ] [ Moaning ]
[ Father McGruder ] Oh , oh , oh , oh !
It that the one with the donkey and the chambermaid ?
No , please !
[ Moaning ]
I understand , Lionel .
Some things a man prefers to do on his own .
[ Moaning continues ]
It 's all part of the grieving process .
[ Moaning ]
[ Footsteps knock loudly ]
Be seeing you , Lionel .
[ Moaning ]
[ Steps bang ] [ Door rumble ]
[ Door rumble ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Lionel groans ]
[ Groans ]
[ Stretching skin crunches ]
[ Bubbling ]
[ Chews crispy ]
[ Radio ] Nijinsky was of what nationality ?
Nijinsky is Russian .
Russian is right , very good . Which number do you want ?
13 ...
13 , he 's going for the Devils number .
I can offer you $ 36 if you take the money in the bank , Peter .
[ Radio broadcast ends ]
[ Car engine noise ]
[ ♪ Cheerful piano score ♪ ]
Lionel ?
[ Railway track noise ]
[ Car engine noise ]
[ Tires screech ]
I dropped a shilling . It must have ...
Rolled down the drain .
I come to see and you shut the door in my face .
You build a big wall . I telephone and you don 't answer .
Why ?
Well , speak to me .
You don 't want to see me anymore ?
It was a mistake .
Sorry .
Goodbye .
[ ♪ Sad piano score ♪ ]
[ Paquita cries ]
Paquita !
Leave me alone .
I 'm sorry !
Leave me alone !
[ Brakes squeak ]
[ Door rumbles ]
Take your hands of her , you creep !
[ Dull bang in the face ] [ Trash can rustles and clatters ]
You know what they 're saying about you , don 't you ?
You 've gone funny in the head !
A real bloody weirdo .
Touch her again and I 'll knock you in the middle of next week .
[ ♪ Sad piano score ♪ ]
[ Radio playing ]
Ohh .
[ Zombies growling ]
[ Footsteps knock ]
[ Static on radio ]
[ Void grunts ]
[ Knock and click ]
Hmm .
[ Bang ]
Ooh !
[ Hiss and rush ]
[ Bangs ]
[ Rumbles clatter ]
[ Demonic voice ] Huh !
[ Click ]
[ Slimy slushy ]
Ew ! ? !
[ Crying ]
Ew !
- [ Smile ] - [ Snarl ]
- [ Snarl ]
[ Cries ]
- [ Baby growls ] - [ Lionel screams ]
- [ Smacks ] - [ Groans ]
[ Coos ]
[ Baby complains ]
[ Complains ]
[ Snarls ]
[ Baby whines ]
[ Growls ]
[ Whines ]
[ Cries ]
Whoa ! [ Clattering ]
[ ♪ Playful piano music ♪ ]
[ Baby cries ]
Ahhh . Cute . Hello . Ahhh .
Whoa aah !
[ Stroller rattles ] [ Lionel ] Whoa !
Ooh !
Ah !
Whoa !
[ Hiss ]
[ Exhale puffing ]
Hello .
Who is a cutie ?
Who 's a cute , little Selwyn then ?
[ Lionel growls in shock ]
[ Groans ]
Hello .
Peek-a-boo .
[ Selwyn cooing ]
[ Selwyn growls ]
[ Selwyn giggles ] Hi hi hi .
[ Tears fabric ]
Whoa oh !
[ Selwyn rejoices ] Whee !
Whoa-haa !
[ Groans ]
[ Stroller rattles ] [ Selwyn chuckle ]
Whoa-haa-haa-haa-haa-ooh !
[ Clattering ]
[ Giggling mischievously ]
Whoa !
[ Screams delightfully ]
[ Thud bang ]
Oh .
[ Cries ]
[ Clatter ]
[ Thud ]
[ Cries ]
[ Clatter ]
[ Laugh malicious ]
Ow !
[ Thud ] Uff !
[ Cooing ]
[ Giggle ]
[ Gasp giggle ]
[ Growls ]
[ Girl scream ]
[ Selwyn ] Ah ah !
[ Whine ]
[ Bang ] [ Cries ]
So I said ...
[ Selwyn cries ] [ ♪ Sarcastic score ♪ ]
[ Plastic bang ]
Yeahhh !
[ Selwyn whine ]
[ Thud ]
[ Clatter ]
[ Gasp ]
[ Selwyn whine ]
[ Groan ]
[ Growl ]
Yeow !
[ Selwyn complains ] Heh !
- Cheep ! - [ Baby squeaks ]
Oh !
[ Selwyn cries ]
[ Crying becomes quieter ]
[ ♪ Ceremony ends fanfare ♪ ]
[ Thuds ]
Hyperactive .
[ ♪ Final chord ♪ ]
[ Selwyn growling screeching ]
[ Laughing ]
So , I tackled this guy , right ?
I brought him down this real bone cruncher .
And the ball rolls free , so I scooped it up .
You know what I did ? I drop kicked from 50 yards out .
[ Laughs ]
God , you should have seen it . Put us three points ahead , gave us the match .
Fantastic !
[ ♪ Sad score ♪ ]
[ Door rumbles ] [ Gasps ]
[ Door closing bangs ]
[ ♪ Scary score ♪ ]
Ohh ! [ ♪ Scary score ♪ ]
Oh ! [ ♪ Fright fades ♪ ]
[ ♪ Fright fades ♪ ]
[ Puff out ]
Hello . Lionel .
[ ♪ Exciting score ♪ ]
Quite a collection of stiffs you got down there .
And I thought you were such a quiet chappie .
Uncle Les , they 're not what you think .
Back off , mate !
Lay a hand on me and I 'll have you for breakfast .
[ Selwyn whines ]
[ Dully punch ]
Sorry , Lionel .
If I don 't report this , I 'll be an accessory after the fact .
[ Hard knocking blows ]
[ Clink ]
[ Rattle ]
I hope they can keep it out of the papers , for you mothers sake .
She always hated a scandal .
This is hard for me , Lionel .
Informing on my sister 's boy and all .
Of course , if I was to keep my mouth shut , I 'd be taking a hell of a risk .
Yeah , put me through to the police , please .
Of course , if I was to ...
Get my fair share of Vera 's estate .
I 'd be more inclined to protect a member of the family .
You want the money .
Detective sergeant Barlow ? I 'd like to report a multiple murder .
Yes , I 'll wait .
The money .
And the house .
Blood is thicker than water , Lionel .
[ ♪ Melancholic score ♪ ]
[ Grunting and moaning ]
[ Selwyn cries ]
[ ♪ Marching music ♪ ]
[ Void screaming ]
Whoa !
Whoa ! Whoa !
Shh !
[ Slosh ]
[ ♪ March vocal ♪ ]
[ Exhale loudly ]
[ Creak ] Whoa !
[ Glass shatters ]
Ah !
[ Banging stomping ]
[ Slamming the door ]
[ Groan ] [ Footsteps ]
[ ♪ Marching music ♪ ] [ Footsteps ]
[ Bottles clink ]
[ Barry ] Yeah , good day . Is Les about ? ...
There you are , bastard !
[ Barry ] Thought we 'd pop over and take a squish at your new digs .
Yeah mate , why not ?
[ Buzzer ] Rip the skin off a few brown ones .
Yeah , we 'll make a night of it . Where are you going ?
- Just for a walk . - No , mate ...
These people want a feast . Let 's get the party going .
We 'll get some savories , right ?
You got rid of those stiffs yet ?
Hey , Les , let 's stick some real music on .
Yeah , coming through Buzzer . Clear the dance floor .
I don 't know what kind of kinky shit you 're into .
But I want those things buried .
[ Footsteps knock ]
[ ♪ Rockabilly-music ♪ ]
[ Short whistle ] [ ♪ Rockabilly-music ♪ ]
[ Cam rattles ]
[ Loud laughter ]
[ Sneeze ]
[ Cross talking party noise ]
[ Rattles and grunting ]
[ Crack and hiss ]
Hang on a minute , mate .
[ Burps ]
[ Slurp ]
No trouble at all .
[ Door banging ]
[ Clicks ]
[ Void roars ]
[ Smack ]
Mmmh ah ! ...
[ Void limps ] [ Grunts ]
[ Les ] Hey ! Hahaha ! Hohoho ! Ho ! Whoa ! [ Rita scream while dancing rock and roll ]
Come on , baby , let 's dance !
No good asking Lionel . He 's nothing like his old man .
He was a real stick man . Used to pull the birds like you wouldn 't believe .
Don 't talk about my father like that .
Ho ho ho ho ...
Ho-ho-ho !
Mmmh ...
Tasty .
Have you got anything else that I can nibble on ?
[ Void growls ]
[ Rumbles ] [ Moans ]
[ Void growls to the music beat ]
Whoa !
So , you know , I throw him a dummy . Fooled him completely .
You got to imagine this is like ... this is like 10 , 15 yards out from the sideline .
Seven of these big buggers are coming towards me .
So what do I do ?
I ... I ... I put my head down ...
And I shocked again . I touched down right between the posts .
You know , the coach reckons I 'm a dead set for the next All Back Trails .
What do you think about that , Paquita ?
You could be going out with the next Bob Scott .
[ Party yelling in the background ]
[ Roger shuffles ] [ Party yelling in the background ]
[ Lawrence gasps ]
I take it back !
[ Void growls ]
I 'm sorry I called Nabokov a pedophile !
[ Shatters ]
Please , get off .
[ Void growls bestially ]
[ Hiccups-grunt ]
Jesus , mate , you shouldn 't take it so personally .
[ Drinks while grunting ]
Om . [ Drinks while grunting ]
[ Bottles clangling ]
Oh ! [ Bottles clangling ]
What do we have here ? A cute , little senorita .
Go away !
Come on , darling , don 't be a party-pooper . Come and have a drink .
- Oh ! - Ow !
I bet you go of like a rocket .
No ! [ Smack ]
Ow !
Oww !
You little bitch , I 'll get you !
Where did she go ? You foreign bitch !
Hey !
[ Paquita panting ]
[ ♪ Mysterious score ♪ ]
[ Heels knocking ]
Hello ?
[ Hiss ]
[ Screams ] Ahhh ! [ Hiss ]
[ Gasp ]
[ Hissing ]
[ Growl ]
- [ Smack ] - Ooh !
[ Scream ]
[ Gasp ]
[ Click ]
[ Growl ]
[ Scream ]
Paquita !
[ Void growls ]
[ Growl ]
[ Gasp ]
Eyeyeyeyey aah !
[ Rumbling ] [ Crunching ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Rattles ]
Paquita .
[ Loud grope ] [ Toddle ]
[ Thud ] [ Panting ]
[ ♪ Dangerous piano score ♪ ]
" Death surrounds him . "
[ Rumble ]
[ Gasp ] [ Grumble ]
[ Lionel ] They 're not ...
[ Whine ]
Dead exactly . They 're just ...
Sort of rotting .
Nurse McTavish .
Father McGruder .
[ Paquita gasps ]
Your mother .
I don 't know what to do , you know .
I don 't know how to stop it .
You must destroy them .
[ Gasp ]
Uh ...
I can 't .
Not mum .
[ Whine ]
That thing is not your mother .
[ Growl ]
[ ♪ Twilight score ♪ ]
[ ♪ Rockabilly-music ♪ ]
Come on , Les , join in .
[ ♪ Sad piano music ♪ ]
[ Baby whine ]
[ Whining sighing ]
[ Whining ]
[ Whine ] [ Grunt ]
[ Cries ]
[ Sob ]
I 'll do it .
No .
[ Complains ]
[ Wailing grunt ]
[ Human-like whining ]
[ Grunting sigh ] [ Loud kiss ]
[ Crackle of syringes ] [ Screaming grunt ]
[ Screaming grunt ]
[ Lionel Sob ]
[ Squeaks ]
[ Sob ]
[ Croaks ]
[ Groans ]
[ Sob ]
[ Whimper ]
[ Selwyn crying in the background ]
[ Howling in the background ]
[ Selwyn cries ]
[ Screams loudly ]
[ Screams even louder ]
[ ♪ Sad piano music ♪ ]
[ Groan ] [ Thud ]
[ Sand patters ]
[ Dull knocks ] [ Scrape ]
[ Gong sound ]
[ ♪ Rockabilly-music ♪ ]
What 's this ?
Two lovebirds flying the coop is it ?
Out of the way uncle Les ! –
You 're not going anywhere , mate . until the house papers come through .
Come on , Lionel .
No , you don 't !
Uh ! Uh !
[ Bang ] Ow !
[ Paquita ] Ah !
[ Smacks ] [ Les ] Ohhh !
Oooooh ! ...
Ahhh ! ... Ah ! Whoa oh ! Ahhh ! ...
[ Bang ] Oof !
[ Rumble ] [ Rattles ]
Ooh ooh ow !
Ahhh !
[ Rumbling ] [ Clattering ]
Come on !
Yeeeaah ! You foreign animal bitch .
[ Bang ]
Time you and I got better acquainted .
[ Rumble ] [ Screech ]
[ Groans ] Ohh .
Ooff !
[ Clanging blow ]
[ Clanging ]
[ Clatter ]
[ Scratch ]
[ Clanging ]
[ ♪ Danger-signaling score ♪ ]
[ Grumble quaky ] [ ♪ Danger-signaling score ♪ ]
[ Grumble quaky ]
- Oh ! - Ow ! Oho !
[ Heels knock ] [ Paquita gasps ]
Yeahhh !
[ Thud ] [ Crackle ]
[ Ah ! Hey ! Hey ! Ahhh ! ] [ Paquita groans ]
[ Boom ] [ Father roars ]
[ Boom ] [ Void roars ]
[ Boom ] [ Nurse screams ]
[ Droning ]
[ Growl ]
[ Roar ]
[ Lionel ] Whoa ! Whoa !
[ Rattle ]
[ Selwyn growls ]
[ Dull knocks ]
[ Smack ]
Help ! Someone !
Please !
[ Zombie roars ]
[ ♪ Enigmatic score ♪ ]
[ Loud door latch ] Uhhh !
[ Loud door latch ]
For God 's sake , run !
Not so loud , mate !
[ Crush ]
[ Explosive bang ]
Ahhh !
[ Void roars ]
Ahh ! [ Void roars ]
Ahh ! Ahh ! Ahh ! [ Fabric tears ]
[ Smacking ] [ Cracking ]
[ Void growls ]
[ Bubbling ]
[ Void roars ]
[ Growls ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Woman screechs ]
[ Screaming , growling , tumult ]
[ Party guest screams ]
[ Crackling tearing ] [ Screaming ]
[ Void growls ]
[ Squashed meat ] [ Rita screams ]
[ Party guest screams ]
[ Void snarls ]
[ Gurgles ] [ Growls ]
[ Slimy sound ] [ Screaming ]
[ Gasps ] [ Thud ]
[ Roar ]
Ow ! Ah ! Ah !
Bastardo !
Bitch ! Ow !
[ Door slams ]
[ Crunches ] [ Burst ]
Aah !
Madre de dios !
[ Both groan ]
[ Knocks ]
[ Paquita gasps ]
Help us !
Bugger that !
[ Glass clinking ] [ Les screams ]
[ Strangled croak ]
[ Crunching tapping stitches ] [ Paquita gasps ]
[ Grunt ]
[ Hissing roar ]
[ Cartilage crackling ] [ Slurp smacky noise ]
Ahh !
[ Strangled screaming ]
[ Gasp ]
[ ♪ Hectic score ♪ ]
Hoo oh !
[ Groaning ]
[ Paquita screams ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Shatter ]
Ahhh !
[ Roaring ]
[ Shatter ]
[ Void growls and roars ]
[ Bang ]
[ Squeak ]
[ Growling ]
Run , Paquita !
[ ♪ Romantically entangled score ♪ ]
[ Growling ]
[ Hard bang ]
[ Les screaming ]
[ Woman screams ]
[ Zombie growls ]
[ Hard bang ]
[ Les ] Whoa ! [ Women screaming ]
[ Another woman screams ]
Whoa !
Help !
[ Woman screams ]
[ Clatters ]
[ Bottles clink ]
Ooh ah !
Help ! Help ! Help !
Ooh !
Comm on !
Ugh !
Yech !
Ow !
Help !
[ Screech ] Ahhh !
[ Hyper bang ]
Ahhh !
[ Roar ]
Ahh ! Ahh !
[ Mandy growls ]
[ Rita screams ]
[ Void growls ]
[ ♪ Highest danger score ♪ ]
[ Hard bang ]
[ ♪ Determined score ♪ ]
[ Heels knock ]
[ Cartilage crackling ]
[ Scream ]
[ Crushing meat ]
[ Crunchy slushy feed party ]
[ Smacking , splashing orgy ]
[ Cartilage crunch ]
[ Slip-up stomper ]
[ Knock and squeak ]
[ Squeak ]
[ Knock and scrub ]
[ Fear crying ]
[ Zombie hustle and bustle ]
[ Vibrating screaming ] Ahhh !
[ Swampy noise ]
[ Slushy ]
[ Demon growls ]
Ahh !
[ Super dull growl ]
[ Void growls and grunts ]
[ Lionel grunting ]
Ah ah ah !
[ Party zombie woman roars ]
[ Lionel gasps ]
[ Void roars ]
[ Door bangs ]
[ Void bangs ]
[ Bang and crack ]
[ Party zombies grunt ]
[ Dishes shattered ]
He ! He !
Hey ...
Some of my best friends are pedophiles !
- [ Zombie growls ] - [ Lawrence screams ]
- [ Zombies eating noise ] - [ Lawrence cries ]
[ Frightening score ]
[ Paquita gasps ]
[ Knife blade sounds smacking knocking against hard material ]
Aah ?
Please don 't kill me .
- [ Gentle score ] - [ Rita cries ]
It 's okay . It 's me .
[ Rita cries ]
[ Zombie rumbling and grunting ]
[ Clatter ]
[ Dull trampling ] [ Father McGruder ] Um !
[ Les ' pitchfork rattles ]
[ Crunching and roaring ]
[ Door bangs ]
[ Father McGruder grunts ]
[ Roar ]
[ Sounds like a whip crack ]
[ Groan ]
That 's a nasty plaque problem you got there , mate .
[ Crunch ]
Ah !
Got a bit of a cavity there , mate .
Hah ha ha ha ha !
Heave ! Heave ! Ho ! [ Crunch ]
[ Growl ]
[ Shattered ] [ Growl ]
You can not ! [ Growl ]
[ Growl ]
[ Knock ] [ Click ]
[ Rita groans and whine ]
[ ♪ High danger score ♪ ]
[ Snarls ] Grrr ...
[ Heels knock ] [ Rita cries ]
[ Sigh ]
[ Rumpled chairs ]
[ Sigh ] Aah !
[ Gasp ] Aah !
Mandy ?
It 's me .
Rita .
Remember ?
[ Growling ] [ Screaming ]
Um ...
[ Growl ]
[ Stuttering gasp ]
[ Hissing gasps ]
Rarara ...
[ Bang and crackle ] [ Groaning ]
[ Cracking ] [ Bubbling growl ]
[ Bubbling growl ]
[ Gurgling grunt ]
[ Tearing crackle ]
[ Grunting growl ]
[ Gurgling ] [ Smack slushy ]
[ Roar ]
[ Lionel screams ] Whoa ! D 'oh !
[ Void growls ] [ Lionel groans ]
[ Tub bang ] [ Void chokes Lionel ]
[ ♪ Danger-signaling score ♪ ]
Whoa aww !
Yuu-yeao ! ...
Ahhh !
[ Chop ]
[ Squeeze ]
[ Crackle ] [ Bubbling ]
[ Thud ] [ ♪ Strum score ♪ ]
Phoo !
[ Tap ] Oof !
[ Mushy ] Hm ? !
[ Whiny grunting ]
[ Grunting growl ] [ Strangled screaming ]
[ Tap ] [ Slurp ] [ Lionel groans ]
[ Smacking bubbling ]
[ Grunts ] Hmm !
[ Grunting roar ]
- Whoa ! - [ Roar ]
[ Crack ]
[ Grunt ]
Shh ! ... [ Grunt ]
Whoa !
[ Clicking ] [ Gasping ]
- [ Thud ] - Whoa !
[ Bang ]
[ Gasp ] [ ♪ Bizarre score ♪ ]
[ ♪ Bizarre score ♪ ]
Whoa-huh !
Whoa-ho !
Ooh !
[ Knock ] [ ♪ Hectic score ♪ ]
[ Rumbling ] [ ♪ Hectic score ♪ ]
[ Gasp ] [ ♪ Hectic score ♪ ]
Ahh ! Ahh ! [ ♪ Hectic score ♪ ]
[ Groan ]
[ Growling ] Rarara ...
[ Smacking ]
[ ♪ Twilight score ♪ ]
[ Groans ] Ahh ! [ ♪ Twilight score ♪ ]
[ Void growls in the background ]
[ Guts smacking and hissing ]
[ Poop ]
Yah !
[ Hiss ]
Ahh !
[ Flush ]
[ Rushing water ]
[ Hiss ] Yah !
[ Slimy noise ]
Ahh !
[ Spit grunt hiss ]
[ Spit ] [ ♪ Hope score ♪ ]
[ Void growl ] [ ♪ Hope score ♪ ]
[ ♪ Hope score ♪ ]
[ Rumbling ] [ Gasp ]
[ Gasp ]
Ahh !
[ Rattle ]
[ Slap ]
[ Rattling ]
[ Quiet scratching ]
[ Hope score ]
[ Creak ]
[ ♪ Longhorn Shaman score ♪ ]
[ Film strip rustles ]
[ Rustles and clatters ]
[ Rumbles ]
[ Bubbling screams ]
[ Groans ]
[ Tinny bang ] Ahh !
Miaow !
[ Squishing meat ] Ahhh !
[ Thud ]
[ Baby ] Ahh ! Ha-ha-ha ! [ Rita screams ]
Ahh ! Miaow !
[ Clatter ]
[ Malicious joy ] Haa-ha-ha-ha !
[ Thud ]
[ Whine ]
[ Creak ]
[ Spring ]
Hehehe ...
[ Air howls ]
[ Gong sound ]
[ Crying ]
[ Splash ]
Oh .
[ Snort ]
[ Click ] [ Engine rattles ]
[ Accelerating rattling ]
[ Scoff ] Hi-hi-hi-hi-hi ... [ Crack ] ...
[ Crack ]
[ Wail ]
[ Whine ]
[ Rattles ]
[ Grinding noise ]
[ Claps ]
[ Clanging ]
[ Baby rejoices ]
[ Thud ] Ow !
Ah ! Ow !
- Hi-hi-hi-hi ... - Ahhh ...
Ahhh ...
[ Grind noise ]
[ Selwyn ] Hi hi hi hi hi ...
Oh ? !
- You mutant little shit ! - [ Selwyn malicious joy ]
Ahhh !
[ ♪ Oracular score ♪ ]
[ Slushy sound ]
[ Scream ]
You 'll be okay .
[ Mandy crackle ]
[ Rita groans ] Ah ! Ah ! Ah !
Let me in , for Christ 's sake ! Let me in !
[ Zombies growling ]
Let me in ! Help me , help !
Paquita , we must .
[ Paquita groans ] Ouch !
Come on , help ! Quickly !
[ Groans ]
Ahhh ! ...
[ Bang ]
Woah !
Ha !
[ Zombie hits the window ] [ Rita ] Ah ah ha !
There 's thousands of them !
What the hell is this ?
Ah ahh ! Ah !
Leave her alone .
She 's been bitten . You know what that means ?
She 's going to turn into one of them !
I won 't ! I won 't !
[ Bangs and clatters ]
Not !
Whoa !
Help me !
W – W –
You want some help ?
[ Clatters ]
[ Les groans ]
[ Bang ]
Ah !
Ahhh ! Ahhh !
[ ♪ Mysterious score ♪ ]
[ Scrub ]
[ Photo clicks ]
[ ♪ Revelation score ♪ ]
[ Clatter ]
[ Banging smacking ]
[ Void 's guts hiss ] [ Screams strangled ]
[ Bangs on the window ]
[ Zombies rumble and knock ]
Whoa !
[ Les ] Ahhh ! [ Paquita ] No !
Stay out of it !
[ Hiss ]
I know what to do . She 's history !
I 've read the comics ! I will bodily dismember her !
[ Paquita screams ]
There 's no room for hysterical women in my unit !
- Ahhh ! ... - Aah !
[ Rushing ]
[ Rasp ]
[ Gasp ]
[ Hiss and bang ]
Ha ! ha !
Haha !
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha !
[ Choking gasps ]
[ Dull Thud ]
[ Creak ] [ Bang ]
- [ Hissing ] - [ Lionel groans ]
Uah ! Ha !
[ Smacking ]
[ Spits ]
[ Groans ]
[ Lionel groans ]
[ Groans ] Oh !
[ Smacking sound ]
[ Slushy sound ]
[ Smacking ]
[ Moans ] Oh oh oh ! [ Smacking ]
[ Lionel knocks ] [ Smacking ]
[ Lionel continues knocking ]
[ Bang ] Oh ahhh !
Ahhh !
[ Clatter ]
[ Guitar riff ]
[ Gasp heavily ]
[ Lionel ] Ahhh !
[ Clinking ]
[ ♪ Zombie waltz score ♪ ]
[ Mushy ]
[ Slimy sound ]
[ Slushy noise ]
[ Zombies bangs the door away ]
[ Woman scream ]
Step right up , you creepo bastards !
Yahh ! Ha-ha-ha ...
Ho-ho ! Ha-ha-ha ...
[ Paquita screams ]
[ Rumble scratch ]
[ Les ] Ha-ha !
[ Woman screech ]
[ Heavy clink ]
Lionel ?
[ Groans ]
Paquita !
[ ♪ Zombie waltz continues ♪ ]
[ Clinking ]
[ Paquita sobs ]
[ Growls ]
[ Woman screech ]
[ Growling ]
[ Flowerpot shattered ] Ahhh !
- [ Woman Scream ] - [ Groaning ]
[ Slimy smacking ]
[ Lionel screams ]
[ Lionel and Paquita screams ]
[ Paquita screech ]
[ Paquita moans ]
[ Lionel screams ]
[ Void guts smacking ]
[ Paquita screams ]
[ Intestinal hiccups ]
Eh !
[ Rita ] Aah ! Aah !
[ Lionel groans ]
[ Voids intestines bubbling ]
[ Cartilage crunch ]
Ooh ! Ahhh !
[ Squashed meat ]
[ Moans ]
[ Grunting ]
Ho !
[ Grunts ]
[ Crackle ]
[ Clatter ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Smacking ] [ Gurgling ]
[ Gurgling ]
[ Slap ] [ Gurgling ]
[ Rumbling ] [ Dull gong ]
Ow !
[ Both moans ] [ Slime hisses ]
[ Rita ] Ha ! Ha !
- [ Rita ] Ha ha ha ha ! Ha ! - [ Zombie ] Ahhh ! Grrr !
Hahaha ! Ha-ha-ha-ha ! ... [ Crank knocks ]
Hahaha ! Hahaha !
[ Crackle ]
[ Hiss ] [ Smacks ]
[ Innards sloshing ]
[ Rita screams ] [ Innards sloshing ]
Just as well someone around here 's got balls , eh , girls ?
Hahaha !
[ Gurgling cry ] Ow !
[ Selwyn malicious laughter ] Hiiihihihi-hihihihi !
[ Selwyn ] Hahaha !
Goddamn , little rug rat !
[ Rumbling ] [ Screaming ]
[ Baby screams ]
[ Les screams ]
[ Selwyn ] Hihihi ! [ Les screams ]
Get out of the way !
[ Lionel ] Whoa !
[ Les ] Ahh ! Ahh !
[ Lionel ] Ahh !
Ooh !
You little maggot !
[ Rita ] Ahh !
Ahh ! Ahh !
Grrr !
Where are you , you little crawler ?
[ Crackle ] [ Rumble ]
[ Groan ] [ Woman ] Ahh !
Oof !
[ Bang and tear ]
[ Paquita ] Ah ! Ohh !
Ah ! Oh-oh !
[ Paquita ] Ahhh !
Ah !
Ooh !
Ahhh ! Ahhh !
[ Growl ]
Ow !
[ Groan ]
[ ♪ Bright piano score ♪ ]
- Aah-ha ! - [ Zombie growls ]
[ Groans ]
- Ahhh ! - [ Zombie growls ]
Nooo !
Aah ! Ahhh !
- [ Zombie growls ] - [ Squishing meat ]
[ ♪ Zombie Waltz score ♪ ]
[ Splash ]
[ Whip crack sound ] Ah ! Ah ! Ahhh !
[ Clinking ]
[ ♪ Cadence ♪ ] [ Clinking ]
Lionel !
[ Light tap ]
[ Crackle rumble quake ]
[ Vera roars ]
Holy Christ ...
Vera .
[ Crackle ]
- [ Vera growls ] - Oh ! Oh ! Oh ! Oh ! Oh ! Oh ! Oh !
[ Les : screams ] Ohhh ! Ohhh ! ... [ Blood splashes ]
[ Resounding moral sermon ]
[ Selwyn gloatingly ] Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha !
[ Rita groans ]
No !
[ Groans ]
[ Void roars ]
Ah ! Ah !
[ Void : demonic growling ]
Ah !
Aah ! Aah ! Aah !
[ Crackling loud tearing ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Roar ]
Muahhh ! Ahhh !
- [ Hit claps ] - [ Ah ! ]
[ Rita ] Ah ! Leave me .
[ Void 's slimy guts ]
Ah ! Ahh !
Yow ! Ha-ha-ha !
[ Claps ]
Ah-ha-ha-haa - - haa ! [ Scratchy sliding ]
[ Bang ]
[ Thundering bang ] [ Slimy sliding ]
Ahhh !
[ Thundering ]
[ Bang ] Ahhh !
Ahhh .
Party 's over .
[ ♪ Mowerwalz ♪ ]
[ Click ] [ ♪ Mowerwalz ♪ ]
[ Engine roar ] [ ♪ Mowerwalz ♪ ]
Ah ! Ah ! Ah ! ...
[ Grinding and bubbling ]
[ Mower squeaks ]
[ Rasping ]
Hooley !
Hoo ! [ Air draft ]
[ Bubbles violently ]
Hoo !
[ Groans ]
[ Air draft ]
[ ♪ Holy Mass Music ♪ ]
[ Hissing angrily ]
[ Air draft hisses ]
[ Grinding and bubbling ]
[ Screams ]
[ Mower rattles louder ]
[ Mower squeaks ] [ Mower rattles louder ]
[ Blade shreds ]
[ Bleat ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Scream ]
[ Rasping ]
[ Mower squeaks ]
Ahhh !
Aah ! Aah !
Aah !
Ugh .
[ Thud ]
[ Click ] [ Rasping ]
[ Rasping ]
[ Croak ]
[ Hiss ]
Hoo !
Hooley !
[ Clang ]
[ Unbalance grinding noise rattling ]
[ Air draft ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Mower squeaks ] [ Screaming ]
[ Mower squeaks ]
[ Splashing , bubbling ]
[ Squeaks ]
[ Chopper chop ]
[ Bone chopper ] [ Slushy ]
[ Mower is running at full speed ]
[ Splashes ] Ahhh !
[ ♪ Mowerwalz ♪ ]
[ Mower squeaks ]
[ Air draft ]
[ Blade shreds ]
[ Mower squeaks ] [ Air draft ]
[ Air draft ]
[ Shredder grinds ]
[ Blades grinding scratching ]
[ Air draft ]
[ Blade shreds ]
[ Mower squeaks ]
[ Splash and Bubbles ]
[ Air draft ]
[ Engine rattle stutters ]
[ Mower rattles ]
[ Mower squeaks ]
[ Air draft ]
[ Hisses ]
[ Bubbles ]
[ ♪ Mowerwalz ends ♪ ] Uuhaahhh !
[ Crack ]
Ah ah ah ah !
[ Les : growling grunt ]
[ Growling ]
[ Growling ] [ Screaming ]
[ Paquita ] Aah-ah-ah !
[ Blocked engine squeaks ]
[ Paquita groans ] Ah ah ahhh !
[ Growling ]
[ Growls ]
[ Les growls ] Oh-oh !
Ahh !
[ Gargles ]
Ahh ! [ Gargles ]
Ahh !
[ Croaks ]
[ Paquita croaks ]
[ Les : painful howl ]
[ Loud spitting ]
[ Les : gravity-distorted voice ] Ho ho ho hooo !
[ Splash ]
Äh ! Oh ohhh oh !
[ Mower runs at full speed ]
Hoo ! [ Mower runs at full speed ]
[ Squeak ] Hoo !
D 'oh !
[ Shoe squeaks ]
[ Steps splash ]
[ Mower motor stops ]
[ Heavy gasping ]
[ Steps knocks ]
[ Growling ]
[ Knocking footsteps ]
Ahhh ! ...
Oo-ah ! [ Click ]
Arr arr arr arrr ! ...
Ahhh ... !
[ Rattles ]
[ Void ] Ra-ra-ra-ra-ra !
Rarara ... !
[ Gasps ]
[ Lionel ] Aahh !
[ Void Growls ] Rara ...
[ Void gargles ] Hoo blublu eh ! ...
Ra rarara ... !
[ Void ] Rarara
... Rrrrarrrarrra ... !
... Rrrrarrrrarrrra ... !
[ Claps ]
[ Roars ]
[ Hiss ]
[ Splash and hiss ]
[ Engine sputters ] Raahraahhh !
[ Smacking hiss ] [ Thud ]
Ah !
[ Barking and hissing ]
[ Crackling and grinding ]
[ Loud spitting ]
[ Crackling heavy panting ]
[ Delusional ] He-he-he ! ...
[ Heel knocks ]
Rita ?
[ Heavy gasp ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Gasps heavily ]
[ Crunches ]
[ Baby growls ]
Oo-ah-ooh ! [ Crackle ]
[ Gasps ] [ Crackle ]
Ew !
Ooh oh ! [ Crackle ]
[ Paquita ] Ohh !
[ Crunches ] Hi-hi-hi ...
No !
Aah !
[ Crunches ] Hi-hi-hi ...
Uh !
[ Evil ] Hi-ha-ha-ha !
[ Lovely ] Hii-ha-ha !
- Ahhh ! - Hi-hi-hi-hi !
[ Bang ]
- [ Rita ] Aah ! Aah ! - Ha-ha-ha ...
Ha-ha-ha-ha ...
- Ahh ! - Ha-ha-ha-ha ...
Ha-ha-ha-ha !
[ Rita ] Aah !
[ Tab squeak ] [ Gas hiss ]
[ Hisses ]
[ Smacks ]
[ Air suction ]
[ Roars and hisses ] Hey !
[ Hiss ]
[ Splash ]
[ Mower rattles ]
[ Spit ]
[ ♪ Lovely score ♪ ] [ Hisses ]
[ Void : Slushy and smacking noise ]
[ Thud ]
[ Squeak ]
Aah ah !
[ Smacks ]
[ Hiss ]
[ Spit ]
Yah ...
Ahhh ! ... [ Mower rattles ]
Ahhh ! ... [ Splash and hiss ]
Ahh !
[ Scratches ]
Ahhh !
Ahh !
No !
You just get out of here .
What ?
Haven 't seen mum yet .
[ Quakes rattling clattering ]
[ Swoosh ]
Aah ! [ Swoosh ]
[ Clink ]
[ Vera roars ]
Ah ! [ Vera roars ]
[ Growling ]
[ Paquita ] Ah ! [ Growling ]
Ah ! [ Growling ]
[ Growling ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Roars ]
[ Hisses ]
Come to mommy , Lionel .
Come on !
[ ♪ Adventurous score ♪ ]
Ah !
[ Steps echo ]
[ Growling ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Clatter ]
[ Crack ]
[ Glass shattered ]
[ Rumbles ]
[ Vera 's anger roars ]
[ Vera rumbles ] [ Vera 's anger roars ]
[ Groans ]
Ahh !
[ Bang echoes ]
[ Groans ]
[ Fire crackles ]
Whoa !
Ah !
[ Paquita ] Ah !
Ah ! [ Vera growls ]
[ Vera growls ]
[ Rumbles ]
No !
[ Vera rumbles ]
[ Vera growls ] [ Vera rumbles ]
You don 't scare me , mum .
[ Growling ]
[ Lionel is out of breath ]
All my life ...
You told me nothing but lies !
[ Growls ]
All that stuff about dad ...
None of that was true !
[ Underwater screaming ]
You drowned them both , mum .
Dad and that ...
Blonde woman , you ...
Caught them together and you killed them , didn 't you ?
How dare you speak to me like that ?
Didn 't you ? !
[ Screaming underwater ]
[ ♪ Sad piano score ♪ ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Sobs ]
Ah !
[ Groaning ] [ ♪ Dramatic score ♪ ]
[ ♪ Dramatic score ♪ ]
[ Vera 's anger roars ] [ Fire crackling ]
Lionel , here quick !
[ Vera 's anger roars ]
Slut !
Ah !
Aahhh !
[ Groans ]
Ah !
[ Vera growls ]
Don 't you touch her !
[ Hisses ]
No ! [ Hisses ]
[ Paquita ] No !
[ Bang with reverb ]
No one will ever love you like your mother .
Ahh !
[ Opening crunches ]
No ! ...
[ Gasps ]
No !
- [ Lionel ] Ahhh ! - Ah ha !
[ Growls ]
- [ Paquita ] No ! - [ Lionel ] Ahh ! Oh !
[ Crunches ]
[ Dull bang ]
No ! ...
[ Gasps ]
Aah !
Ahh !
[ Paquita ] No ho ho !
[ Grunts ]
No !
Ah ha !
Such a good boy .
[ Paquita ] No ho ho ! ... [ Demon mom ] Ho , ho , ho , ...
No ho ho !
[ Gasps ]
Ah ha ha ha !
Ah ha !
[ Crunches ]
[ Growls ] Ha ha !
[ Sobs ] [ Knocks ]
[ Sobs ]
[ Growls ] Ha - - ha-ha-ha !
[ Growls ]
[ Groans ]
Ha ha ha !
[ Mom groans ]
[ Groans ]
[ Burst out and plash ]
[ Cries ]
[ Crackle ]
[ Roars ] Ow !
[ Blood rushing ]
[ Fire hisses ]
[ Bubble ] [ Simmer ]
Ooh !
Oh !
Ohh !
[ Paquita groans ]
[ Drums ]
Whoa ! hui ! Aah ha hui !
Aah !
Ah ah !
Ooh ha !
[ Lionel moans ] [ Belt squeaks ]
Aah !
[ Siren ]
Ooh ah ! [ Siren ]
[ Emergency crew talks ]
[ ♪ Shrill score ♪ ]
[ Fire crackles ]
[ Hiss ]
[ Selwyn cries ]
[ Deployment team commands ]
Ohh !
[ ♪ Romantic score ♪ ]
No !
♪ The sign of love ♪
♪ Has cost its toll ♪
♪ The truth foretold ♪
♪ Is now revealed ♪
♪ Its mystery ♪
♪ Our destiny ♪
♪ The stars and moon ♪
♪ The sign of love ♪
♪ Has come at last ♪
♪ 2 lonely hearts ♪
♪ Are in the past ♪
♪ It blazes bright ♪
♪ Love 's blinding light ♪
♪ Through darkest night ♪
♪ And floods the room ♪
♪ The stars and moon ♪
♪ No more darkness ♪
♪ Time is precious ♪
♪ Love is immortal ♪
♪ The stars and moon ♪
♪ In the end there is love ♪
♪ The sign of love ♪
♪ Our time has come ♪
♪ The stars and moon ♪
♪ Will shine for us ♪
♪ The stars and the moon ♪
♪ Are guiding us ♪
♪ We follow the sign ♪
♪ To perfect love ♪
♪ The sign of love ♪
♪ Our time has come ♪
♪ The stars and moon ♪
♪ Will shine for us ♪
♪ The stars and the moon ♪
♪ Are guiding us ♪
♪ We follow the sign ♪ ♪ To perfect love ♪